Which faction do you want to join?
Many ladies have recruited me,
but it's impossible for
me to choose just one.
Therefore...
I'm going to join all the factions.
Huh?
What?
And you think you're worth it?
Who knows?
Say it again.
You think you're worthy of joint
faction membership?
I do not know.
But in order to be someone you wish
me to be, I shall give it my all!
Then please prove your worth.
Coming from a man, I'm not...
Please, Shilto!
He totally changes his reaction
between men and women.
We're going to test your skills.
For you, Miss Shilto,
I can even pull off four consecutive
all-nighters, which my maid has banned!
THE UNPRECEDENTED TROUBLEMAKER
Kunon Gurion's taking on the
three factions in a magic battle?!
He's still new, isn't he?
Why make a trainee like that do this?
But apparently this guy is the
student of Zeonly Finroll.
What?! He's Master Zeonly's student?!
I've got to see it!
Yes, I simply must see it!
I hope Kunon's going to be okay.
If he gets hurt, Reyes
can heal him, right?
He brought it on himself,
but I guess I shall.
I'll go, too.
I'm gonna beat him up!
Causing such an uproar is what I'd
expect from the student on Zeon.
I'll do my best to meet your
expectations, Professor Sayfie.
If I win, how about we get a delicious
parfait at a café as a reward?
Do not hit on your professor.
Oh?
That's beautiful. Made of magic silver?
Yes. It's my lucky charm.
Everyone's so intense.
They're the top sorcerers
in the advanced class.
Especially...
Sandra. She's here, too.
If she's in this, then I'm worried
about the collateral damage.
Collateral?
She's good at bold moves
but sucks at control.
She'll mow down everyone in sight.
Really?
Somehow, I can't imagine
that Kunon would lose.
True.
I kind of get that.
This is a quasi-barrier to
guard against attacking spells.
The match is over when this magic
circle is broken or someone yields.
Who wants to go first?
I'll go!
Why do you get to decide that?
I'm going first.
Going by the order determined
by the representatives,
Ability should go first.
I don't think that matters anymore.
That's right! Stay out of this, uggo!
I'm not ugly.
Please don't fight over me,
my beautiful fairies and the other one.
You're the cause of all this!
Are you referring to
me as "the other one"?!
I can take you all on at once, ladies.
Huh?
What?
Say what?
Come again?
I'm confident I can win regardless
of how many come at me.
If it's the first time.
What?
Did he just say all at once?
That's crazy talk.
Did he say four of them at once?
What is Kunon thinking?
As long as he doesn't die,
it's not a problem.
I can heal him.
Here's the roster of
the factions this year.
There may be some changes later.
What's the matter?
Actually, a first-year student seems
to be causing a commotion about this.
That brat, huh?
Let us begin.
I'm excited!
He's so cocky.
Are you really sure?
Yes!
Cocky, cocky, cocky!
You shouldn't provoke them, Kunon.
How is he planning to win?
What? He has to break
that magic circle, right?
I don't believe he's
learned any attack spells.
Oh!
Please begin!
He's only got two
elementary spells, right?
He's Zeonly's student, huh? Yikes.
What is he up to?
I guess I'll wait and see.
A-ori.
And it's a very basic one.
Multiply.
Color.
That's...
The red fog he used
against Professor Soff.
Wait, what?
This is A-ori, too?
It's clinging to me.
Hey, don't get my clothes dirty!
I love this outfit!
Calm down! It's just fog!
He's obscuring our sight so he can attack?
What the heck is this?
Coloring it must be a bluff.
It's a basic water spell, A-ori.
It's only water.
I was wrong!
It's my turn now! Just you watch...
Ew, I don't like this.
Is this... slime?
You got me! I yield!
We lose, Kunon Gurion.
Okay.
Huh? It's over?
Just because it rained?
Why didn't they counterattack?
They lost on purpose
because they wanted Kunon?
I don't think so.
In the name of their factions,
they wouldn't dare lose to a first-year.
That magic circle...
Why use the quasi-barrier?
The rain obviously passed
through the barrier.
I passed the test, didn't I?
You didn't hold back, did you?
Who's going to clean this up?
Have no fear.
It'll disappear when I release it.
Are you all right, my beautiful mermaids?
A-ori.
Here's my apology for making you cold.
Think of this as the warmth of my heart.
It's warm?
Here you go.
Get lost!
Would you like one?
So what was that red rain, exactly?
Well, who knows?
What did you do?
It's sticky water!
You know, it's like slime rain.
Oh, the color is irrelevant.
It just needed to be distinguishable.
If you're showered with it,
a counterattack is out of question.
It gets in your mouth,
so you can't chant a spell.
Let alone breathe...
So Sandra and the others
were right to admit defeat.
Then why didn't that magic
circle repel your attack?
What I used was not an
attack spell, but an elementary A-ori.
The amount of magical
power used was too small?
So it didn't recognize it as
an attack, and it let it through.
You knew the properties
of the magic circle?
Yes. I've done magic battles with that
magic circle many times with my master.
With Zeonly?!
No need to hold back.
Hit me with everything you've got.
I'll teach you the depth of earth magic.
Okay, I'll try!
All right, bring it!
The Zeonly...
...lost?
Is that true?
I cannot lie to you.
I only won the first battle,
and after the second time, he'd hit me
preemptively and I kept losing.
So, if you wait and see, you lose.
It's nastier than I thought.
No one can beat you in the first battle.
So that's what you meant.
We'll allow your joint membership.
Yes! Now I can spend my school life
with you without anyone interfering.
Just thinking about that makes
my heart soar until dawn!
I'm pretty sure three self-nominated
joint memberships is unheard of.
We've got someone truly out of the box.
Before joining the factions,
you should talk to the seniors
you embarrassed in front of everyone.
Yes. As a gentleman, I'd love to
get to know those three ladies.
And another person.
You mean Cassis?
I'd happily invite ladies any day, but...
Well, the thing is...
The heart... of a maiden?
The heart of a maiden.
Who knew there was a man...
no, a woman like that?
Oh, there you are, Kunon!
What happened after that?
What was that red rain?
The whole school is talking about it.
Did you solve the issue
with the factions?
They approved joint membership?!
That's amazing, Kunon!
I still have a long way to go.
I am so ashamed of my
ungentlemanly behavior.
I can't look Her Highness in the eye.
Hey, Mirika!
Are you ready?
You'd better be.
I told you I'd be fine
by myself, Brother Lyle.
It's a big day for the vice captain.
It's only natural I watch over
it as the captain, right?
How are you, Kunon?
Today, I'm finally taking the exam
for the knighthood department
at the senior school for nobles.
Next! Mirika Hughlia!
Yes!
Begin!
There you go. That's my vice captain.
Match over!
Mirika Hughlia!
I will become a woman worthy of you.
So please do your best
at the magic school.
What?
Her Highness, in the
knighthood department?
Master Kunon! It's getting cold,
so let's head inside.
Master Kunon?
What's up?
It's time for dinner.
Already?
Shall I bring you a fresh warm one?
Oh.
No, it's fine.
I'll drink it at night,
so take it to my room.
It's the milk tea you
make for me with love.
That's right.
There's no tea in it, though.
Rinko. Do you ever cut
yourself with a knife?
I'm a pro, so I don't.
I see. Please be careful.
Is everything okay?
You're awfully kind today, Master Kunon.
I'm always kind,
because I'm a gentleman.
My dear fiancée.
How are you?
I suppose I should congratulate you on
enrolling in the knighthood department
at the senior school for nobles.
But I'm very worried.
You must be training hard every day,
like your life depends on it.
There may be times when you get hurt.
I want to support you and cheer for you,
but I do not wish to see you suffer.
Well, not that I can really see.
Please, please, do not
push yourself too hard.
I will write to you.
Again and again, many times.
Please don't forget about me.
Not a day goes by when
I don't think about you.
Your Kunon Gurion, with eternal love.
He's thinking of me so much.
I'm fine!
I've grown so strong that even
a bear can't scare me away!
When you come back, you'll be surprised.
How could I forget about you?
I'm always thinking about you, too.
"With eternal love," oh, my!
"P.S., I've made a few dozen
more female friends at school."
Huh? Isn't that a lot?!
"I've encountered a mysterious
lady with the heart of a maiden."
"I intend to learn about more ladies
and become a gentleman who
is worthy of Your Highness."
K-Kunon! You don't have to
work too hard on that front!
Oh, good morning, sea birds
playing in the shallows.
I just know that I was
born to heal your hearts.
Hey, Kunon!
Cassis!
As an apology for my rude behavior,
I'd like to invite you to lunch,
and the gentleman in me is jumping
as if to dance so early in the morning.
Please accept my invitation.
Shut up!
I'm the type to hold grudge.
I only came because the
representative told me to!
Kunon!
Mr. Bael wants you to join him
in developing a magic tool.
Wonderful!
I will dedicate the knowledge of magic
tools I learned from my master to you!
Hey, now! I was here first!
Get lost, you uggo!
I'm not ugly!
As an earth sorcerer,
I'm interested in Zeonly's knowledge.
Will you share it with me as well?
Hey, Kunon!
Fight me one more time!
I'm not going to lose this time!
Oh, shut it, shut it!
What?!
Ugly mugs, you all need to get lost!
What a mess...
It's impossible to join
three factions, isn't it?
I'm going to make pills of shi-shilla.
Do you want to write a report on it?
Of course I do, Miss Reyes!
It seems Kunon joined all three factions.
It's unprecedented.
The first troublemaker since Zeonly.
I highly welcome it.
So, I'm going on a search for a
shipwreck with the representative.
You interested?
A shipwreck?!
I would love to come along!
Weigh anchor! Set sail!
I can't suppress my curiosity!